http://www.saltybrine.com/privacy.htm#privacy

Award-Winning
File Synchronization,
File
Replication, File Backup, Duplicate File Finder Software and more.
Privacy Policy for Salty Brine Software Sites
(which include but are not limited to: saltybrine.com,
foldermatch.com, folderclone.com, textfrompdf.com, htmlmatch.com)
If you require any more information or have any questions
about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us through our support
form.
At Salty Brine Software we value the privacy of our
visitors. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal
information that is received and collected by Salty Brine Software
sites: (www.saltybrine.com, www.foldermatch.com, www.folderclone.com,
www.textfrompdf.com, www.htmlmatch.com) and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, Salty Brine Software sites
make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet
protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP),
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends,
administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic
information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any
information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Salty Brine Software web sites do not use cookies.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to
serve ads on Salty Brine Software web sites.
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve
ads to users based on their visit to Salty Brine Software web sites: (www.saltybrine.com, www.foldermatch.com, www.folderclone.com, www.textfrompdf.com, www.htmlmatch.com) and  other sites
on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by
visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL
- http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web
beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....
Google Adsense
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use
technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Salty Brine Software
web sites send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP
address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the
effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising
content that you see.
Salty Brine Software web sites have no access to or
control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of
these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices
as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.saltybrine.com's privacy policy does
not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers
or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through
your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie
management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective
websites.
Copyright  Salty Brine Software
- All rights
reserved.
Home
